gamepix.com 2019-11-01

# GamePix' Privacy Policy

If you’re reading this, it’s because you, (hereinafter “Data Subject”), want to know what information we, GamePix S.r.l., with registered office in via Belluno, 1 00161 Rome Italy , Company registration No. 12327731001 qualifying as Data Controller, are collecting on www.gamepix.com and on GamePix App, what we’re doing with it, and what are the rights related to the processing of such Personal Data you’ll be entitled to, If you have any questions or concerns after reading this, please email us at info@gamepix.com.

This Privacy Policy applies to the GamePix website and games located at www.gamepix.com (“Site”) and on GamePix App (“App”), including the Apps and games available on social media/networks. This notice describes only our online information collection and use practices at this Site and App; it doesn’t apply to information we collect about you offline (such as over the phone) or in different situations (such as through email correspondence).

This privacy policy is effective as of 25 May, 2018, in accordance with the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data and other applicable data protection laws (“GDPR”). In the future, our Site, our App or our practices may change, and if appropriate, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect the changes. We’ll post the updated version here, and we’ll notify you if we think the changes will significantly impact the treatment of information you have already provided.

#### Information We Collect

The Information you provide can be listed as follows:  
– Passive tracking technologies. This Site and App uses passive tracking technologies to log non-identifiable information such as: IP address, browser type, and Site and App usage (for example: what pages are accessed, how often, referring/exit pages and URLs).

– Cookies. We also employ “cookies” or similar technologies that provide additional functionality to the Site and App and help us analyze Site and App usage more accurately. Remember: You can set your browser to reject cookies, but if you do, some features on our Site and App will not function normally. Please see the Gamepix’s Cookie Policy accessible [here](http://www.gamepix.com/cookie-policy/).

– Demographic Data Report by Google Analytics Advertising Features. This information is used to track your provenience. You can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features downloading a plugin available here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

For more and detailed information, please read our cookie policy [here](http://www.gamepix.com/cookie-policy/).

#### Children

We take many special precautions to protect the privacy of children. If you are located in the European Economic Area and under the age of 16, you must not use the Service for any purpose unless with your parental or legal guardian’s prior consent.

We may collect some information (like IP address, mobile device unique device identifier (hereto referred as “UDID” or “Device ID”), OS, etc.) automatically and use technology like cookies to provide functionality and support our operations.

We do not ask for more personal information than is necessary for a child to participate in an activity.

Parents can contact us if they have any question on the collection, use or sharing of their children’s information.

#### For which Purposes we process your Information and the corresponding legal basis

We collect your information for the following purposes:

PURPOSES | LEGAL BASIS  
---|---  
• to provide you with the service, to respond to your requests and provide customer service | • the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract or to take steps at the request of the data subject  
• communicate your information to some of our partners (Advertisement providers and partners. i.e. Google Ireland Inc.) | • your consent before using our service or starting playing one of our games  
  
#### Links and Third Parties

From time to time we may include at the Site & App links to other websites and apps as a service to you. The third party sites and apps are operated by companies that are outside of our control, and your activities at those sites and apps will be governed by the policies and practices of those third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of these third parties before disclosing any personally identifiable information, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites and apps.

We sometimes work with third parties to add features or advertisements to our Site and App. These third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit certain pages of our Site and App, or collect cookies that they have previously placed, along with the URL of the page you visited. We do not control those third parties or their use of data. In some cases we may provide tools for you to limit data sent to third parties. This privacy policy does not cover those third parties’ use of data.

GamePix uses one or more companies to place advertisements for our products and services and those of third-parties on our Site and third-party sites. Cookies and other technologies such as Web beacons or tags are used to measure the effectiveness of our ads and to determine the display of content and advertising to you based on your interests both on our site , as well as on third- party sites where you may visit. To support this interest based advertising solution, we, and companies who we have contracted with, may use anonymous information about your visits to our and other Web sites. The information collected and used by this process is always anonymous, and does not enable any third-party to identify you individually. Although it is our hope that you find the display of advertising to you based on your anonymous interests valuable, if you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can always opt-out of this activity by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by clicking [ http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

#### How long we store your information

In principle we will retain your information as long as required or permitted by applicable law. Afterwards, we will remove your Personal Data from our systems and records and/or take steps to properly anonymize it so that you can no longer be identified from it.

In particular, we will store your information according to the following table:

PURPOSES | DATA RETENTION  
---|---  
• to provide you with the service, to respond to your requests and provide customer service | • information will be stored only for the time necessary to provide you with the service  
  
#### Your Rights

As a Data Subject, you are entitled to request:

– right of access: you have the right to obtain from us confirmation as to whether or not Personal Data concerning you is being processed, and, where that is the case, to request access to the Personal Data. The access information includes – inter alia – the purposes of the processing, the categories of Personal Data concerned, and the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the Personal Data have been or will be disclosed;

– right to rectification: you have the right to obtain from the controller without undue delay the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning you. Taking into account the purposes of the processing, you have the right to have incomplete Personal Data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement;  
– right to erasure: you have the right to obtain from the controller the erasure of Personal Data;

– right to restriction of processing: you have the right to request the restriction of processing your Personal Data;

– right to data portability: you have the right to receive the Personal Data concerning you which you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and you have the right to transmit those Personal Data to another entity without hindrance from us;

– right to object: you have the right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, at any time to the processing of your Personal Data by us and we can be required to no longer process your Personal Data.

In particular, if you are receiving GamePix email advertisements and no longer wish to receive those email messages, you may opt out at the time you receive the message by following the instructions in that email. Please allow ten days for your request to be processed.

If you do not agree with the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy, it may be best to limit your level of interaction with our Site and App, which could include simply not providing us with personal information. While this will limit the services that our Site and App are able to provide (chat, friends lists, challenges, etc.), most of the games will remain playable. This option may be best for those who do not wish to provide the mandatory information required to set up an account.

For complaints or requests regarding the use of personal information you submit to us, please contact us at info@gamepix.com.
